A Guide to the Records of the Instructive Visiting Nurses Association 1902-1999
Virginia Commonwealth University, Tompkins-McCaw Library
- Organization and Professional Staff
  - Organization
    - Directors Information (Box-folder 29.9)
    - Recruitment for Director 1971 (Box-folder 29.10)
    - Blue Cross-Blue Shield (Box-folder 29.11)
    - Blue Cross/Blue Shield 1982 (Box-folder 29.12)
    - Medicare (Box-folder 29.13)
    - Hospital Nurse Coordinator (Box-folder 29.14)
    - Insurance (Box-folder 29.15)
    - Public Relations 1948-1950 (Box-folder 29.16)
    - Public Relations (Box-folder 29.17)
      1952-1953, 1955-1958, 1961, 1968
    - Public Relations 1970-1971 (Box-folder 29.18)
    - Service Pins (Box-folder 29.19)
    - Lillian D. Wald (Box-folder 29.20)
    - Lillian D. Wald (Box-folder 29.21)
    - Lillian D. Wald of Henry Street (Box-folder 29.22)
    - Statistics 1975 (Box-folder 29.23)
    - Compliance to Civil Rights Act 1964 (Box-folder 29.24)
    - Oregon Hill Neighborhood Council 1967, 1969 (Box-folder 30.1)
    - Oregon Hill Neighborhood Council 1966-1973 (Box-folder 30.2)
    - Richmond Area Community Council 1965-1968 (Box-folder 30.3)
    - MCV Education 1963, 1972 (Box-folder 30.4)
    - Staff meeting minutes 1966, 1975 (Box-folder 30.5)
    - National League of Nursing Certificates 1955-1980 (Box-folder 30.6)
    - Health Survey of Richmond 1939 (Box-folder 30.7)
    - Public Health Reports 1950-1959 (Box-folder 30.8)
    - Long Range Planning (Box-folder 30.9)
    - South Richmond Study 1949 (Box-folder 30.10)
    - Agency Relations Manual-United Way (Box-folder 30.11)
  - Financial
    - Budget Requests to UGF 1963 (Box-folder 30.12)
    - Budget Requests to UGF 1964 (Box-folder 30.13)
    - Budget Requests to UGF 1965 (Box-folder 30.14)
    - Leeper File 1960 (Box-folder 30.15)
    - Celia Loram (Box-folder 30.16)
    - Satko File (Box-folder 30.17)
    - Budget Requests To UGF 1978 (Box-folder 31.1)
    - Budget Requests to UGF 1979 (Box-folder 31.2)
    - Budget Requests to UGF 1980 (Box-folder 31.3)
    - Budget Requests to UGF 1981 (Box-folder 31.4)
    - Budget Requests to UGF 1982 (Box-folder 31.5)
    - Budget Requests to UGF 1982 (Box-folder 31.6)
    - UGF Correspondence 1963-1966, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 31.7)
    - IVNA Budget 1951-1966 (Box-folder 31.8)
    - IVNA Tax File (Box-folder 31.9)
    - IVNA Treasurer Report (Box-folder 31.10)
    - United Givers Fund Correspondence and Reports 1966-1982 (Box-folder 32.1)
    - Financial Requests to city 1939-1950 (Box-folder 32.2)
    - IVNA Health Services-IRS 1989 (Box-folder 32.3)
    - IVNA IRS (Department of Treasury) (Box-folder 32.4)
  - Mergers
    - Pre-merger discussion, IVNA-City of Richmond 1950-1952 (Box-folder 32.5)
    - Contracts, IVNA-City of Richmond, Combined Service 1952 (Box-folder 32.6)
    - Annual Reports, Combined Service 1954-1962, 1965 (Box-folder 32.7)
    - Reappraisal 1957 (Box-folder 32.8)
    - Separation IVNA-City of Richmond 1964-1966 (Box-folder 32.9)
    - Post Separation 1966-1969, 1980 (Box-folder 32.10)
    - South Richmond Community Nursing Service 1949-1950 (Box-folder 32.11)
    - Proposal to combine Homemaker-Home Health Care services 1968-1969 (Box-folder 32.12)
    - Operation Reality, Lowe-Freeman 1960-1961 (Box-folder 33.1)
    - Public Health-University of Pittsburgh, Lowe 1960-1961 (Box-folder 33.2)
    - Freeman-IVNA Correspondence 1954-1964 (Box-folder 33.3)
    - Richmond Family Nursing Competence Scale, Lowe 1958-1963 (Box-folder 33.4)
    - Merger 1964-1969 (Box-folder 33.5)
    - IVNA Nursing Services to City of Richmond 1965-1967 (Box-folder 33.6)
    - Staff Council Meeting Concerning Separation (Box-folder 33.7)
    - Joint Nursing Service 1952-1953 (Box-folder 33.8)
    - Merger (Box-folder 33.9)
  - Staff Studies, Papers, Miscellaneous
    - Appraising Family Public Health Nursing, M. Lowe 1959-1963 (Box-folder 33.10)
    - Appraising Family Public Health Nursing, M. Lowe 1959-1963 (Box-folder 33.11)
    - Appraising Family Public Health Nursing, M. Lowe 1959-1963 (Box-folder 33.12)
    - Surgeon General's Consultant Group on Nursing (USPHS) 1961 (Box-folder 34.1)
    - Evaluation of Public Health Nursing 1961 (Box-folder 34.2)
    - Speeches, M. Lowe 1962 (Box-folder 34.3)
    - Teaching Schedule, Topic, M. Lowe 1960-1963 (Box-folder 34.4)
    - Team Nursing Study 1970 (Box-folder 34.5)
    - Breakin April 26, 1969 (Box-folder 34.6)
    - Family Coping Index and Form 1964 (Box-folder 34.7)
    - Surgeon's General's Correspondence 1961-1963 (Box-folder 34.8)
    - Henrico County (Box-folder 34.9)
    - Henrico County 1967-1970 (Box-folder 34.10)
    - Henrico County Statistical Report (Suppl. to Service Report) (Box-folder 34.11)
    - Virginia Landmarks (Box-folder 34.12)
    - Self Study (Box-folder 34.13)
    - IVNA: Home Care Study-Dr. Spencer 1965 (Box-folder 34.14)
    - Workshop Report Community Organization and Leadership (Box-folder 34.15)
    - Cost Study (Box-folder 35.1)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Ruth Freeman (Box-folder 35.2)
    - IVNA-City Nursing Service and John Hopkins School of Hygiene 1959 (Box-folder 35.3)
    - Ruth Freeman Study (Box-folder 35.4)
    - P.H.N. Survey Richmond-A.B. Wilson (Box-folder 35.5)
    - Studies Related to Richmond PH/Nursing 1957 (Box-folder 35.6)
    - Outline Homemaker-Home Health Aide Study, April 1969 (Box-folder 35.7)
    - IVNA-CHS Study 1 1945-1946 (Box-folder 35.8)
    - IVNA-CHS Study 2 1945-1946 (Box-folder 35.9)
    - Clippings-Re: Sinai Project (Box-folder 36.1)
    - Public Health Organization and Administration Part 1 (1 of 2) 1945 (Box 36)
    - Public Health Organization and Administration Part 2 (2 of 2) (Box 36)
    - A Report on The Study of Costs in Public Health Nursing(2 copies) (Box 36)
    - South Richmond Study Richmond Area Community Council, May 1949 (Box 36)
    - Evaluation Report of the Home Care Services 1980 (Box 36)
- Series 5: Photographs
  - Photographs (Box 37)
  - Photographs (Box 38)
- Series 6: Miscellany
  - Guest Book (Box-folder 39.1)
  - Scrapbook 1901-1920s (Box 39)
  - Morbidity Statistical Volume 1946, oversized (Box 40)
  - Morbidity Statistical Volume, Discharged Cases 1946-1952, oversized (Box 40)
  - Scrapbooks 1920s, 1940s, 1970s, 3 scrapbooks (Box 41)
  - Scrapbooks 1919-1960, oversized, 8 scrapbooks (Box 42)
  - Newspaper clippings (Box 42)